## **CV**

# LEONARDO JOHN PANSIPANSI

**COMPUTER ENGINEERING** 

Contact No. +639451486169 Email: ljpansipansi@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/ljfanxi Wesite: ljfanxi.github.io/website

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I aim to bring value as a dedicated team member to an institution devoted to continual professional advancement, providing a career that is both challenging and rewarding, allowing me to leverage my expertise and skills. In my recent role as an individual researcher, I was tasked with an in-depth study on autonomous navigation robotics. This experience deepened my understanding of integrating components, ensuring compatibility across various operating systems, software applications, programming languages, and sensor devices. The importance of understanding and being resourceful has become evident to me through my experience.

# EDUCATIONAL ATTAINMENT

2013 - 2018

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering Asian College Dumaguete

2020 - 2022

Master of Science in Computer Information and Communication Engineering



### **AWARDS**

Korea Institute of Information and Commucation Engineering(KIICE), 2021

Object Detection and Localization on Map using Multi-Camera and Lidar PointCloud

**Excellent Paper Award** 

14<sup>th</sup> International Conference on Future Informtion and Communication Engineering(ICFICE), 2022

Object Detection and Localization on Map using Multi-Camera and Lidar PointCloud

**Excellent Paper Award** 

### **COMPETITIONS**

TRANSBOT Competition at Asian College Dumaguete 2017 - **Champion** 

Robotics Competition 2017 - Philippine Institute of Computer Engineering, SU Line Following Robot - **1st Runner-Up** 

Robotics Competition 2018 Philippine Institute of Computer Engineering, SU Line Following and Sumo Robot - Champion and 1st Runner-Up

# VOCATIONAL CERTIFICATE

National Certificate IV (NC4) Microsoft.NET Computer Programming Training

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

January 2018 - March 2018

Intern at APL Computer Solution

- Recovering corrupted data
- Creating POS and InventoryManagement System using SQL Server and VB.NET

#### August 2018 - November 2019

Autonomous Vehicle Lidar and Image Annotation Remote Job

Quality Assurance

#### December 2019 - Febuary 2022

Kunsan National University Lab

- Autonomous Navigation Robot Researcher
- Data analyze of lidar point cloud and image data.

### PERSONAL PROJECT

**Loan Management System Desktop Application -** using python and excel as database.

**File Sharing Website -** using python-django, sqlite3, html and css.

**Personal Portfolio -** my website using html and css.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **Python**

- Machine Learning
- Image Processing Open CV
- Desktop Application
- Web Application Django for Back End
- Data Analysis and Visualization

#### **SQL Server**

 Relational Database Management

HTML/CSS - Front End

**MATLAB** 

**Autonomous Navigation Robot** 

**Robot Operating System** 

**Ubuntu Linux / Windows** 

#### **SOFT SKILL**

- Problem Solving
- Self learning
- Resourceful
- Creativity
- Flexible